Guide to the John Burroughs Papers, 1850-1991 (bulk 1860-1921)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES V. CORRESPONDENCE: INCOMING, 1850-1928
  - Others: Miscellaneous, by Category
    - From Artists
      - Cole, Timothy, (3 letters) (Folder 42.3)
      - Fuertes, Louis Agassiz, (2 letters) (Folder 42.3)
      - Gibson, W. Hamilton (Folder 42.4)
      - Gray, C. S. (Folder 42.4)
      - Harrison, Henry (Folder 42.4)
      - Heffley, Eugene (Folder 42.4)
      - Johnson, Adelaide (Folder 42.5)
      - Learned, Leila Sprague, (2 letters) (Folder 42.5)
      - Lwoff-Parlaghy, Vilma, Princess (Folder 42.5)
      - Murphy, J. Francis (Folder 42.5)
      - Pietro, Cartaino Sciarrino, (2 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 42.6)
      - Pritchard, Zarh H., (2 letters) (Folder 42.6)
      - Ricketson, Walter (Folder 42.7)
      - Rouland, Orlando (Folder 42.7)
      - Secor, David Pell (Folder 42.7)
      - Smedley, Will Larymore, (3 letters) (Folder 42.7)
      - Stanton, Lucy (Folder 42.7)
    - Requesting Autographs
      - Day - McCaleb, (4 letters) (Folder 42.8)
      - Miller - Young, (5 letters) (Folder 42.9)
    - Regarding Birds
      - Collins, Henry H. (Folder 54.16)
      - Farnham, R. A. (Folder 54.16)
      - Gibbs, Mrs. Almon J., (2 letters) (Folder 54.16)
      - Gowanlock, J. Nelson (Folder 54.16)
      - Granger, Charles H. (Folder 54.16)
      - Greenough, Horatio S. (Folder 54.16)
      - Hemmingway, Georgie (Folder 54.16)
      - Hildreth, R.B. (Folder 54.16)
      - Johnston, Alma Calder (Folder 54.16)
      - Miller, William H. and Elizabeth (Folder 54.16)
      - Miller, William K. (Folder 54.16)
      - Mills, William C. (Folder 54.16)
      - Oakes, R. A., (2 letters) (Folder 54.16)
      - Park, A. F. (Folder 54.16)
      - Pratt, George B., (2 letters) (Folder 54.16)
      - Ritscher, Lucie J., (2 letters) (Folder 54.16)
      - Robbins, Susan Brown (Folder 54.16)
      - Skinner, Harriet Hayes (Folder 54.16)
      - White, Charles E. (Folder 54.16)
      - Wier, Bertha Barker (Folder 54.16)
      - Willson, William (Folder 54.16)
    - Regarding his Birthday
      - Corson, Mary Frances (Folder 42.10)
      - Ellis, C. J. (Dentist) (Folder 42.10)
      - Fargo, DeVerne, (4 letters) (Folder 42.11)
      - Foreman, Edward R. (Folder 42.10)
      - Foreman, Edward R. and Louise M. (Folder 42.10)
      - Honey, Delia Darling (Folder 42.12)
      - Hutchinson, Thomas (Folder 42.12)
      - Lewis, Charles H. (Folder 42.12)
      - Miller, Pauline P. (Mrs. Charles T. Miller) (Folder 42.12)
      - Parkhurst, Wellington E. (Folder 42.13)
      - Phillips, Henry M. (Folder 42.13)
      - Savage, William Rutherford (Folder 42.13)
      - Shackelford, Esther B. (Mrs. G. R. P. Shackelford) (Folder 42.13)
    - From Californians
      - Church, Walt Le Noir (Folder 42.14)
      - Mills, Gertrude C. (Folder 42.14)
      - Newkirk, Garrett (Folder 42.14)
      - Reed, Elizabeth A. (Folder 42.14)
      - Rhoads, J. B. (Folder 42.14)
      - Sellers, Fay H. (Folder 42.14)
      - Sherwood, Martin (Folder 42.14)
      - Stone, George E. and May V. (Folder 42.14)
      - Wilson, Sherman B., (2 letters) (Folder 42.14)
    - From Canadians
      - Grove, F. P. (Folder 42.15)
      - Lauder, Alma Dick (Folder 42.15)
      - O'Higgins, Harvey J. (Folder 42.15)
      - Pattullo, Thomas Dufferin (Folder 42.15)
      - St. Arnauld, Marie (Folder 42.15)
      - Strangman, Charles (Folder 42.15)
    - From Classmates
      - Bouton, Charles W. (Folder 42.16)
      - Carpenter, T. A., (2 letters) (Folder 42.16)
      - Hough, Annie Gould, (2 letters) (Folder 42.16)
      - McCarthy, Edward Dorr (Folder 42.16)
      - Nash, H. J. (Folder 42.16)
      - Wilcox, Franklin A. (Folder 42.16)
    - From Clergy
      - Belknap, A. Jay (Folder 42.17)
      - Collyer, Robert (Folder 42.17)
      - Cooke, George Willis (Folder 42.17)
      - Crook, George V. (Folder 42.17)
      - Nott, Charles D. (Folder 42.17)
      - Smith, W. R. L. (Folder 42.17)
      - Townsend, James G. (Folder 42.17)
      - Van Antwerp, W. H. (Folder 42.17)
      - Watson, Arthur J. (Folder 42.17)
    - Expressing Criticism
      - Allen, Francis H. (Folder 43.1)
      - Berger, Henry (Folder 43.1)
      - Coulson, S. B. (Folder 43.1)
      - Cropley, W. G. (Folder 43.1)
      - Goodale, Dora Read (Folder 43.1)
      - Greenwald, Isidor (Folder 43.1)
      - Haydon, Walter (Folder 43.1)
      - Huffaker, E. C. (Folder 43.1)
      - McGilton, Alice (Folder 43.1)
      - Meert, Victor E. (Folder 43.1)
      - Moore, A. R. (Folder 43.1)
      - Muckley, Henry C. (Folder 43.1)
      - Nagle, Augustus F. (Folder 43.1)
      - Newberry, C. E. (Folder 43.1)
      - Pierce, G. W. (Folder 43.1)
      - Sponsler, William H., (2 letters) (Folder 43.1)
      - Storrs, Caryl B. (Folder 43.1)
      - Thompson, John (Folder 43.1)
      - Thompson, William (Folder 43.1)
      - Winch, George A. (Folder 43.1)
    - From Editors
      - Abbott, Lyman — Outlook (Folder 43.2)
      - Blake, Harrison G. O. — Thoreau Papers (Folder 43.3)
      - Browne, Francis Fisher — The Dial, (5 letters) (Folder 43.4)
      - Cabot, James Eliot — Emerson Papers, (2 letters) (Folder 43.5)
      - Clapp, Henry — Saturday Press (Folder 43.6)
      - Fields, James T. — Atlantic Monthly, (4 letters) (Folder 43.7)
      - Gilder, Richard Watson — Century Magazine, (7 letters) (Folder 43.8)
      - Johnson, Robert Underwood — Century Magazine, (13 letters) (Folder 43.9)
      - Johnson, Rossiter — Little Classics (Folder 43.10)
      - Lathrop, George Parsons — Atlantic Monthly (Folder 43.11)
      - Mabie, Hamilton Wright — Outlook, (4 letters) (Folder 43.12)
      - Montgomery, George Edgar, (2 letters) (Folder 43.13)
      - Page, Walter Hines — Atlantic Monthly, (2 letters) (Folder 43.14)
      - Perry, Bliss — Atlantic Monthly, (7 letters) (Folder 43.15)
      - Whitney, Caspar — Outing, (2 letters, 1 note) (Folder 54.18)
    - From England
      - Brown, Leonard M. (Folder 43.16)
      - Chase, Lewis (Folder 43.16)
      - Coward, L. A. (Folder 43.16)
      - Deloplaine, Blanche L. (Folder 43.16)
      - Ellis, Henry Daw (Folder 43.16)
      - Gandy, Thomas (Folder 43.16)
      - Haydon, W. T. (Folder 43.16)
      - Isaacs, A. (Folder 43.17)
      - [?], Katharine, (2 letters) (Folder 43.17)
      - Miller, W. H. (Folder 43.17)
      - Parker, A. J. (Folder 43.17)
      - Rowe, Charles R., (2 letters) (Folder 43.17)
      - Strang, William, (2 letters) (Folder 43.17)
      - Tirebuck, Margaret E. (Folder 43.17)
    - From Fiction Writers
      - Allen, James Lane (Folder 43.18)
      - Bacheller, Irving (5 Letters) (Folder 43.18)
      - Dodge, Mary Mapes, (2 letters) (Folder 43.18)
      - Garland, Hamlin, (8 letters) (Folder 43.19)
      - Hale, Edward Everett, (2 letters) (Folder 43.19)
      - Hall, Ruth (Folder 43.19)
      - Jewett, Sarah Orne (Folder 43.20)
      - Paine, Albert Bigelow, (2 letters) (Folder 43.20)
      - Preston, Margaret J. (Folder 43.20)
      - Riddle, A. G. (Albert Gallatin), (3 letters) (Folder 43.20)
      - Sprague, Mary A., (7 letters) (Folder 43.21)
      - Stuart, Ruth McEnery, (2 letters) (Folder 43.21)
    - Regarding Plants and Flowers
      - Burbank, Luther (Folder 44.1)
      - Coville, Frederick V. (Folder 44.1)
      - Elliott, Florence V. (Folder 44.1)
      - Heywood, Sarah H. (Folder 44.1)
      - King, Jane A. (Folder 44.1)
      - Lindley, John W. (Folder 44.1)
      - Niles, Grace G., (2 letters) (Folder 44.1)
      - Rounthwaite Henry M. (Folder 44.1)
      - Smith, Robert (Folder 44.1)
      - Stockman, Ruth (Folder 44.1)
      - Warren, Elizabeth J., (3 letters) (Folder 44.1)
    - From Hawaii
      - Alexander, W. D. (Folder 44.2)
      - Hollister, Paul M. (Folder 44.2)
      - Judd, Agnes H. B. (Folder 44.2)
      - Moses, Stanford E. (Folder 44.2)
      - Winslow, Anne Goodwin, (2 letters) (Folder 44.2)
      - Withington, Anne (Folder 44.2)
    - Regarding his Health
      - Bresnahan, J. H. (Folder 54.17)
      - Chandler, Russell H., (2 letters) (Folder 54.17)
      - Kahn, R. L. (Folder 54.17)
      - Kast, Ludwig, (2 letters) (Folder 54.17)
      - Kellog, J. H. (Folder 54.17)
      - Leland, Mrs. E. H. (Folder 54.17)
      - Waldstein, L., (2 letters) (Folder 54.17)
    - From Lawyers
      - Burt, George Noyes (Folder 44.3)
      - Clearwater, A. T., (5 letters) (Folder 44.3)
      - Dill, Charles G. (Folder 44.3)
      - Ingersoll, Robert G. (Folder 44.3)
      - Kassel, Charles (Folder 44.3)
      - McNeill, John C. (Folder 44.3)
      - Parker, Alton Brooks (Folder 44.3)
      - Peters, T. McClure (Folder 44.3)
      - Talbot, Frank, (4 letters) (Folder 44.3)
    - From Naturalists
      - Baynes, Ernest Harold, (3 letters) (Folder 44.4)
      - Gladden, George, (5 letters) (Folder 44.4)
      - Job, Herbert K. (Folder 44.4)
      - Merriam, Clinton Hart, (3 letters) (Folder 44.4)
      - Seton, Ernest Thompson, (6 letters) (Folder 44.4)
      - Sharp, Dallas Lore, (3 letters) (Folder 44.4)
    - Regarding Nature Fakers
      - Barrus, Clara - to John Finley (Folder 55.5)
      - Bigelow, Edward F. (Folder 44.5)
      - Boynton, Henry Walcott (Folder 44.5)
      - Chamberlain, William Isaac (Folder 44.5)
      - Chapman, Frank M - to Caspar Whitney (Folder 55.5)
      - Cummings, Helen W. (Folder 44.5)
      - Curtis, Carlton C. (Folder 44.5)
      - Davis, Harper (Folder 44.5)
      - Day, Ernest Ellsworth (Folder 44.5)
      - Deane, Ruthven, (2 letters) (Folder 44.5)
      - Deming, Horace E. (Folder 55.5)
      - Figgins, J.D. (Jesse Dade) (Folder 55.5)
      - Fraser, W. A. (Folder 44.5)
      - Greenslet, Ferris (Folder 44.5)
      - Long, William J. (to Mr. Anderson) (Folder 44.5)
      - McGaffey, Ernest (Folder 44.5)
      - McGaffey, Ernest (Folder 55.5)
      - Page, Walter H. (Folder 55.5)
      - Parke, Anna Nelson (Folder 44.5)
      - Pomeroy, H. S., (2 letters) (Folder 44.5)
      - Roys, Cyrus A. (Folder 44.5)
      - Russell, Selwyn A. (Folder 44.5)
      - Schur, Arthur P. (Folder 44.5)
      - Smith, Charles D. (Folder 44.5)
      - Stone, Andrew J. (Folder 44.5)
      - Towne, Edward S. (Folder 44.5)
      - Whitney, Caspar (Folder 55.5)
    - From Neighbors
      - Bonschur, Emilie, (4 letters) (Folder 44.6)
      - Coons, Herman (Folder 44.6)
      - Cox, James J., (2 letters) (Folder 44.6)
      - Fish, Mary (Folder 44.6)
      - Hazen, J. T. (Folder 44.6)
      - Herr, Mary C. (Folder 44.6)
      - Judd, Jeanette (Folder 44.6)
      - Knaub, Fred G. (Folder 44.6)
      - Little, John W. (Folder 44.6)
      - Paddock, Cornelia Hill (Folder 44.6)
      - Shane, George C. (Folder 44.6)
      - Smith, John R. (Folder 44.6)
      - Thomson, William J. (Folder 44.6)
      - Van Benschoten, William (Folder 44.6)
      - Van Deusen, Eleanor C. (Folder 44.6)
      - Van Keuren, J. W., (2 letters) (Folder 44.6)
      - Ventres, D. B., (2 letters) (Folder 44.6)
    - From Ornithologists
      - Brewster, William, (4 letters) (Folder 44.7)
      - Chapman, Frank M., (10 letters) (Folder 44.7)
      - Cowes, Elliott (Folder 44.7)
      - Eckstrom, Fannie Hardy, (7 letters) (Folder 44.7)
      - Hardy, Manly, (2 letters) (Folder 44.7)
      - Hardy, Walter M. (Folder 44.7)
      - Flagg, Wilson, (2 letters) (Folder 44.7)
      - Hamlin, Charles E. (Folder 44.7)
      - Hodge, C. F. (Folder 44.7)
      - Wright, Mabel Osgood (Folder 44.7)
    - From Overseas
      - Ball, Robert (Folder 45.1)
      - Berwig, Elise (Folder 45.1)
      - Ferrero, Felice (Folder 45.1)
      - Hamilton, Alexander G. (Folder 45.1)
      - Hanibullah, Mohommad (Folder 45.1)
      - Hight, George A., (photocopy) (Folder 45.1)
      - LaVarre, William J. (Folder 45.1)
      - Reed, Eliza M. (Folder 45.1)
    - From Personal Friends
      - Bock, William E. (Folder 45.2)
      - Bock, Bertha M., (2 letters) (Folder 45.2)
      - Booth, Sara A., (2 letters) (Folder 45.2)
      - Davis, Fanny E. (Folder 45.2)
      - Harriman, Mary (Folder 45.2)
      - Newton, Mary (Folder 45.2)
      - Shipman, Melvina (Folder 45.2)
    - From Poets
      - Abbey, Henry (Folder 45.3)
      - DeKay, Charles (Folder 45.3)
      - Franklin, Jean Dwight (Folder 45.3)
      - Gates, Mary C. (Folder 45.3)
      - Hubner, Charles W., (2 letters) (Folder 45.3)
      - Irvine, J. P. (Folder 45.3)
      - Kenyon, James B., (2 letters) (Folder 45.4)
      - Kidson, Robert B. (Folder 45.4)
      - Markham, Edwin (Folder 45.4)
      - Mifflin, Floyd (Folder 45.4)
      - Nicholl, Louise Townsend (Folder 45.4)
      - Stedman, Edmund Clarence, (3 letters) (Folder 45.4)
      - Terry, Edward Hicks (Folder 45.4)
      - Waterman, Nixon (Folder 45.4)
      - Williams, Earl, (2 letters) (Folder 45.4)
      - Wood, Chester (Folder 45.4)
    - From Relatives and Would-be Relatives
      - Hutton, Marion I. (Folder 45.5)
      - Linnenbauk, Mrs. Jacob (Folder 45.5)
      - De Olagaray, Mrs. J. M. (Folder 45.5)
      - Perry, Burroughs Frederick (Folder 45.5)
    - With Requests
      - Brooks, V. W., (2 letters) (Folder 45.6)
      - Calhoun, H. C. (Folder 45.6)
      - Davis, A. M. (Folder 45.6)
      - Edwards, Helene (Folder 45.6)
      - Ely, Robert Erskine (Folder 45.6)
      - Kitson, Henry (Folder 45.6)
      - Love, Robertus, (2 letters) (Folder 45.6)
      - Markscheffel, Louise (Folder 45.6)
      - Pattee, Fred Lewis, (2 letters) (Folder 45.6)
      - Patton, C. L. (Folder 45.6)
      - Pottle, Bion B. (Folder 45.6)
      - Smith, M. F. (Folder 45.6)
      - Sturtevant, W. (Folder 45.6)
      - Varney, George Leon (Folder 45.6)
      - Winchell, F. M. (Folder 45.6)
      - Zukerman, David (Folder 45.6)
    - About Theodore Roosevelt
      - Laughlin, Harry H. (Folder 45.7)
      - Schroer, Dr. H. (Folder 45.7)
      - Stevens, Lillian T. (Folder 45.7)
      - Wills, Mrs. E. K. (Folder 45.7)
      - Winkler, F. (Folder 45.7)
    - From School Children, Teachers and Administrators
      - Ballard High School (Folder 45.8)
      - Barker, Virgil B. (Folder 45.8)
      - Beaudry, Maude (Folder 45.8)
      - Berne High School (Folder 45.8)
      - Bickford, Faith (Folder 45.8)
      - Brisbee, Joseph B. (Folder 45.8)
      - Bookhout, T. C. (Folder 45.8)
      - Cox, Edward L. (Folder 45.8)
      - Elliot, Jane (Folder 45.8)
      - Frant, Yetta (Folder 45.8)
      - Harlow, Arthur (Folder 45.8)
      - Henderson School (Folder 45.8)
      - Night letters from School Children (Folder 45.8)
      - Patri, Angelo (Folder 45.8)
      - Rindge, Clara (Folder 45.8)
      - Sproull, Herbert (Folder 45.8)
      - Stearns Jr., G. R. (Folder 45.8)
      - Sukey, Paul (Folder 45.8)
      - Sullivan, Winifred M. (Folder 45.8)
      - Swift, T. Dean (Folder 45.8)
      - Van Meter, Bessie (Folder 45.8)
      - White, Arthur Eliot (Folder 45.8)
    - Regarding Science Questions
      - Bann, James (Folder 45.9)
      - Davis, J.D. (Folder 45.9)
      - Downer, John Rulon (Folder 45.9)
      - Dunham, H. F. (Folder 45.9)
      - Fontaine, Edmond (Folder 45.9)
      - Gorton, David Allyn (Folder 45.9)
      - Kruckeberg, Jennie (Folder 45.9)
      - Norris, Richard H. (Folder 45.9)
      - Opdycke, E. B. (Folder 45.9)
      - Rees, Forest R. (Folder 45.9)
      - Wright, Wendell L. (Folder 45.9)
    - From Scientists
      - Beebe, Charles William, (2 letters) (Folder 45.10)
      - Brigham, Albert Perry (Folder 45.10)
      - Hornaday, William T., (2 letters) (Folder 45.10)
      - Peckham, George W. (Folder 45.10)
      - Yerkes, Robert Mearns (Folder 45.10)
    - From Scotland
      - Horne, John (Folder 45.11)
      - Scoular, Robert (Folder 45.11)
      - Wilson, David Alec (Folder 45.11)
    - From Slabsides Visitors
      - Adams, Daniel and Evangeline (Folder 45.12)
      - Arnold, Amelia A. (Folder 45.12)
      - Baker, Smith (Folder 45.12)
      - Belding, Alice (Folder 45.12)
      - Binder, Rudolph M. (Folder 45.12)
      - Damon, Louis A. (Folder 45.12)
      - Dillon, Emma P. (Folder 45.12)
      - Ellis, Prudence Helen (Folder 45.12)
      - Hinman, Olive (Folder 45.12)
      - Hix, Melvin, (2 letters) (Folder 45.12)
      - Hughes, Mrs. E. R. (Folder 45.12)
      - Johnson, Edna (Folder 45.12)
      - Lee, James Melvin (Folder 45.12)
      - MacDonald, Mary H. (Folder 45.12)
      - Mathewson, Chester A. (Folder 45.12)
      - Monroe, Will S. (Folder 45.12)
      - Roberts, James O. (Folder 45.12)
      - Rose, Fanny Tousey (Folder 45.12)
      - Taylor, Lucy (Folder 45.12)
      - Thompson, H. H. (Folder 45.12)
      - Wardle, Caroline V. G. (Folder 45.12)
    - From Soldiers
      - Ellis, Fenwick L. (Folder 45.13)
      - Kellogg, Albert B. (Folder 45.13)
    - From Former Students
      - Denton, Helen, (2 postcards) (Folder 46.1)
      - Mead, Fanny Allaben (Folder 46.1)
      - Smith, Tammy, (Transcript only) (Folder 46.1)
    - From Teachers
      - Adler, Felix, (1 letter) (Folder 46.2)
      - Albert, Edna, (12 letters) (Folder 46.3)
      - Burt, Mary E., (11 letters) (Folder 46.4)
      - Chubb, Percival (Folder 46.5)
      - Dean, Alletta F. (Folder 46.5)
      - Friday, Julia Bassett (Folder 46.5)
      - Gilbert, J. H. (Folder 46.5)
      - Hall, J. M. (Folder 46.5)
      - Kost, Henry (Folder 46.5)
      - Lanier, Elizabeth M. (Folder 46.5)
      - Oliver, Emily J. (Folder 46.5)
      - Oliver, Emily J. (Folder 46.5)
      - Oliver, James, (2 letters) (Folder 46.5)
      - Robinson, Winifred (Folder 46.5)
      - Romig, Edna Davis (Folder 46.5)
      - Murphy, Eva, (2 letters) (Folder 46.5)
      - Smith, D. S., (6 letters) (Folder 46.5)
      - Sweeney, Paul J. (Folder 46.5)
      - Tryon, W. P. (Folder 46.5)
    - From Travel Writers
      - Dellenbaugh, Frederick S. (Folder 46.6)
      - Johnson, Clifton, (2 letters - copies only) (Folder 46.6)
      - Longstreth, T. Morris (Folder 46.6)
      - Roberts, Morley (Folder 46.6)
    - From Students, Alumnae and Staff of Vassar
      - Haight, Helen I. (VC 1898) (Folder 46.7)
      - Hall, Lucy M. (Physician) (Folder 46.7)
      - McNary, Sarah J. (English Dept.) (Folder 46.7)
      - Rogers, Ruth (Folder 46.7)
      - Whiting, Anne H. (VC 1916) (Folder 46.7)
    - Regarding "Waiting"
      - Allen, Willis Boyd, (3 letters) (Folder 46.8)
      - Anonymous (Folder 46.8)
      - Bartlett, Alfred (Folder 46.8)
      - Benedict, Mary Cadwallader (Folder 46.9)
      - Bellazzi, Mr. and Mrs. R. P. (Folder 46.9)
      - Brown, Margery Keeler (Folder 46.9)
      - Butler, Hattie C. (Folder 46.9)
      - Chandler, Mary Alderson (Folder 46.10)
      - Hart, F. H. (Folder 46.10)
      - Lee, Jeannette (Folder 46.10)
      - McDonaugh, Mary C. (Folder 46.10)
      - Rainsford, H. J. (Folder 46.10)
      - Thayer, M. A. (Folder 46.10)
      - Tuttle, Emma Rood (Folder 46.11)
      - Ware, George Wilde (Folder 46.11)
      - Woods, Charles C. (Folder 46.11)
      - Wright, Merle St. Croix, (fragment) (Folder 46.11)
      - Yergason, Katherine B. (Folder 46.11)
    - Regarding Wartime
      - Canfield, Katharine C. (Folder 46.12)
      - Chew, John A. (Folder 46.12)
      - Daniels, Josephus (Secretary of the Navy) (Folder 46.12)
      - Dickie, Perry (Folder 46.12)
      - Dickinson, Edward (Folder 46.12)
      - Dunne, James (Folder 46.12)
      - Eshleman, C. H. (Folder 46.12)
      - Forster, Henry A. (Folder 46.12)
      - Gibbs, David (Folder 46.12)
      - Hixon, Anne (Folder 46.12)
      - Hobart, R. A. (Folder 46.12)
      - McCaddon, Joseph T. (Folder 46.12)
      - McNeely, W. M. (Folder 46.12)
      - Miller, M. (Folder 46.12)
      - New York Tribune Associate Editor (Folder 46.12)
      - Osborne, Joseph S. (Folder 46.12)
      - Schmidt, Karl (Folder 46.12)
      - Stratton, C. L. (Folder 46.12)
      - Timewell, C. A. (Folder 46.12)
      - Tooker, L. Frank (Folder 46.12)
    - Regarding Washington
      - Arnold, J. G. (Folder 46.13)
      - Baker, Mary Cole, (2 letters) (Folder 46.13)
      - Barstow, Eliza Hillis (Folder 46.13)
      - Dascomb, Celia N. French (Folder 46.13)
      - Longan, A. W., (2 letters) (Folder 46.13)
      - Loomis, E. J. (Folder 46.14)
      - McCulloch, Hugh (Folder 46.14)
      - Miller, Julia (Folder 46.14)
      - Peck, D. B. (Folder 46.14)
      - Peck, E. S. (Folder 46.14)
      - Price, M. (Folder 46.15)
      - Sherwin, M. H., (2 letters) (Folder 46.15)
      - Snead, Fayetta (Folder 46.15)
      - Turner, Emory S. (Folder 46.16)
      - Viele, M. L. (Folder 46.16)
      - West, Henry Litchfield (Folder 46.16)
    - Regarding Walt Whitman
      - Bazalgette, Léon (Folder 47.1)
      - Beach, Juliette Hayward (Folder 47.1)
      - Browne-Gillies, Blanche (Folder 47.1)
      - Bucke, Richard Maurice (Folder 47.1)
      - Cummings, Edward (Folder 47.1)
      - Dyer, L.H. (Folder 47.1)
      - Goode, Brown (Folder 47.1)
      - Guernsey, Fred R. (Folder 47.1)
      - Harrison, Mary (Folder 47.1)
      - Johnston, John (Folder 47.2)
      - Johnston, J. H. (Folder 47.2)
      - Macalister, Alexander (Folder 47.2)
      - Mallinkrodt, James F. (Folder 47.2)
      - Marshall, Louise (Folder 47.2)
      - Marshall, Maria A. (Folder 47.2)
      - Phillips, George S. (Folder 47.2)
      - Price, Helen E. (Folder 47.2)
      - Quinlan, Walter B. (Folder 47.2)
      - Schmidt, Rudolph (Folder 47.2)
      - Stuart, Helen (Folder 47.2)
      - Trimble, W.H. (Folder 47.2)
      - Wilde, Isabel (Folder 47.2)
    - Regarding Wildlife
      - Bruce, David D. (Folder 47.3)
      - Cleghorn, Allen (Folder 47.3)
      - Curtis, Henry S. (Folder 47.3)
      - Fair, Paul J. (Folder 47.4)
      - Hall, Charles H. (Folder 47.4)
      - Lenpp, Francis E. (Folder 47.4)
      - Lloyd, J. William, (2 letters) (Folder 47.4)
      - Nelson, Henry (Folder 47.5)
      - Perry, Jeanette Barbour (Folder 47.5)
      - Platt, F. G. (Folder 47.5)
      - Smith, Sidney (Folder 47.6)
      - Thompson, W. Gilman (Folder 47.6)
      - Tomkies, James Scott (Folder 47.6)
      - Wilson, Lewis G. (Folder 47.6)
    - From Women Writers
      - Becker, May Lamberton (Folder 47.7)
      - Brower, Edith (Folder 47.7)
      - Dowden, Elizabeth Dickinson West (via Martin W. Sampson) (Folder 47.7)
      - Irwin, Mabel MacCoy (Folder 47.7)
      - Tarbell, Ida M. (Folder 47.7)
      - Waln, Nora (Folder 64.9)
      - Wheeler, Candace (Folder 47.7)
    - From Writers
      - Benton, Charles E., (3 letters) (Folder 47.8)
      - Benton, Joel, (2 letters 3 postcards) (Folder 47.8)
      - Brown, Joseph Brownlee, (4 letters) (Folder 47.8)
      - Emerson, Edward W., (2 letters) (Folder 47.9)
      - Hubbard, Elbert (Folder 47.9)
      - Kelly, Allen (Folder 47.9)
      - Lloyd, Henry D., (2 letters) (Folder 47.9)
      - Sanborn, Frank B. (Folder 47.10)
      - Sinclair, Upton (Folder 47.10)
      - Trine, Ralph Waldo, (2 letters) (Folder 47.10)
      - Wasson, David A., (3 letters) (Folder 47.10)
- SERIES VI. CORRESPONDENCE: MISCELLANEOUS, 1860-1929
  - To Ursula Burroughs
    - Benton, Myron, 1896-1900; (11 letters (9 are photocopies), 3 with transcripts, 1 article, 1 obituary, 1 annotated) (Folder 47.11)
    - Corbin, Abigail, 1878; (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 47.12)
    - North, Amanda, 1860-1916; (5 letters, 1 check, annotated) (Folder 47.13)
    - North, Uriah, 1864-Aug 1867; (5 letters, 5 annotated) (Folder 47.14)
    - North, Uriah, Sep 1867-1878; (7 letters, 7 annotated) (Folder 47.15)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore, 12 Dec 1898; (1 photocopy) (Folder 50.7)
    - Regarding Ashoken Reservoir, 1909; (3 letters, 1 postcard, 1 annotated) (Folder 47.16)
    - Family, (6 letters, 1 postcard, 1 empty envelope, 6 annotated) (Folder 48.1)
    - Friends (Albert-Coons), (8 letters, 1 postcard, 5 annotated) (Folder 48.2)
    - Friends (DeLoach-Mackay), (7 letters, 1 article, 5 annotated) (Folder 48.3)
    - Friends (Platt-Van Buren), (7 letters, 1 copy of letter, 4 annotated) (Folder 48.4)